You all killed my husband.
Dong, I thought you were dead.
Dong.
Have you also heard,
that she killed those
who kidnapped her?
What?
Keep your mouth shut if you
don't want to end up like your friend.
You're an assassin, aren't you?
What if I was the one
who killed your friends?
Like I've said,
Yaji is not our enemy here.
The purpose of this launch
is to expose the enemy.
We're not the only sniper here.
There are others.
Mr. Roswell. Ma'am Aemie.
Boss.
Damn! You guys are
looking so handsome.
Good thing they
finally started arriving.
I don't know anyone
here except them.
Oh.
Hey.
Kaizer.
Are you okay?
Why are you slapping yourself?
No, I'm fine, Ma'am Aemie.
Just trying to wake myself up.
Good thing they got us
all seated at the same table.
Keep me company, okay?
Psst. Hey.
So boring.
I guess I'll just take a selfie.
Like I've said,
Yaji isn't our enemy here.
The purpose of this launch
is to expose the enemy.
Fifteen minutes to go.
Huh?
What's that, Dong?
Sebastian's bored.
Bye!
Twelve minutes.
I'll just wait for you guys.
Why are you counting down, Dong?
Just eat, wife.
Ten minutes.
What's going on?
Why is everyone leaving?
I bet you came here
to see your daughter.
Why haven't you joined them?
No.
Actually, I came
here to see you dead.
Just kidding.
Don't take it too seriously.
It might come true.
Well, see you around, Mrs. Ferrer.
Anyways, if you want
to know my name,
Cyd Garnett.
Noted.
Mr. Roswell.
Mr. Ferrer.
Good to see you here.
Thank you.
This is Violet Swansea.
Hello, good evening.
Is she the wife of
Caileigh's father?
I thought Caileigh's
mother was dead.
Good evening, young lady.
Oh.
I wasn't able to formally
introduce my wife to you, sir,
the last time we met.
This is my wife,
Aemie Ferrer-Roswell.
The daughter of
Alyana Heartily-Ferrer.
Zeke?
What does this mean, kid?
Welcome to our party.
Violet, I thought you
were on our side?
Sorry to disappoint you, Alyana.
I'm the one who killed your
family, the Roswell family too.
And I'm planning to
continue this set-up
through the next
generations of your families.
You've gone crazy!
Yes!
I'm crazy!
Crazily in love
with your husband.
So long!
Alyana Heartily-Ferrer!
Ladies and gentlemen,
please join me in welcoming
Mrs. Aemie Roswell,
as we celebrate this exciting
launch in the toy industry.
Eiji and Roswell need
to know about this.
Mei.
How about you just
ditch your plan?
What?
Are you out of your mind, Cass?
She's absolutely fine, sis.
I'll take care of my
sister, Miss Heather.
What are you doing here, Max?
Where are you going, Cass?
I will obey the
order of the Queen.
As we celebrate this exciting
launch in the toy industry.
Let's give her a round of applause.
Good luck, wife.
Sis, don't!
Oh, shucks.
There's a blackout!
- Guys, what's happening?
- Zeke?
This isn't part of the plan.
- Where are you?
- Just hold on to me tightly, Ma'am Aemie.
Come on.
Where are we going?
Just hold on.
- Okay.
- We'll explain everything later.
Queen.
I know where Aemie
and the others are.
I'll take you to them.
Who are you?
I'm Fauzia Arcadia, ma'am.
Arcadia?
By chance, you know
Simon Arcadia and his wife?
Pauline Crest.
Yes, ma'am.
They're my parents.
Let's go.
Fauzia, where are you going?
You traitorous bitch!
I'm not a traitor.
I've never been your ally.
Fuck, I don't
have time for this.
Let's go.
Come on.
Where do you think you're going?
You cannot run away from me.
Violet!
You bitch!
Let's go back! Don't you
want to go back?
Is this part of the program?
Go, Jacob!
Do your best, hurry!
Come on, Ma'am Aemie.
- You were awesome back there, man!
- Let's go.
You killed him?
Guardian angel!
Shit. Fauzia.
Mommy!
- I'll just get the car.
- Mommy!
- Mommy, what happened?
- Vash! Hurry!
What happened?
- Mommy, who did this to you?
- Vash, hurry!
Baby Ae.
- Mommy.
- Your dad...
Alive.
Dad?
- Alive.
- Alive?
I don't understand you.
Mommy, what?
Please, Baby Ae.
[mumbling]
Mommy, who did this to you?
Who did this to you, Mommy?
Who? Mommy!
Roswell.
Zeke?
Wife.
So, any update
on their condition?
Are they finally dead yet?
What?
Goddamn it!
What happened?
They were rushed
to the hospital.
They're in the
operating room now.
I'll handle Arcadia.
Who wants to join Valkyrie?
Can I?
No, not you.
It's too dangerous.
I'll go with her.
We're not even Swansea.
Why are you volunteering?
We want to take down
Roswell, don't we?
Whoever wants him gone,
I'm helping them.
Roswells, Yaji.
Two groups full of dumb members.
Let them fight
each other to death.
And administer this to
Arcadia in the hospital.
It's for hypertension.
But it's also known
to weaken memories
of traumatic experiences
once given shortly
before the event.
Why don't we just kill her?
Because that's how I want it!
Let's go?
I'll go with you, Valkyrie.
I wanna know what
happened to Ezekiel.
Suit yourself.
Zeke.
Did you—
Did you really do that to Mommy?
No.
Is there a problem,
Ezekiel Roswell?
What?
None.
I'm here to see my
daughter and wife.
Huh?
What is Uncle talking about?
Caileigh isn't here, right, Momo?
How would I know?
Just shut up, Wakwak!
Aemie.
Your father is here.
Fa—
Father?
What?
What do you mean?
Mr. Ferrer...
is your biological father.
I don't— I don't understand you.
- Mommy!
- Your dad. Alive.
Dad?
Alive?
I remember.
That's why,
Mommy said,
she was saying
"dad" and "alive."
Because she's
trying to tell me that...
you're still alive.
Excuse me.
I can't believe this.
You're here.
Alive.
You're Amesyl, right?
I'm your uncle.
Your father, Alexander,
was my cousin.
I'm sorry, but I won't believe it
until Auntie says it herself.
Cuz.
Believe him.
Mommy told me before
she lost consciousness.
Doc?
- Doc.
What's the news?
Ms. Arcadia is fine.
She has a lot of broken bones, but
she'll recover from them in no time.
What about Auntie Yana?
As for Ms. Heartily,
the operation is still ongoing.
The gunshot wound
caused a lot of blood loss.
She's in a critical
state as of now,
but we're doing
everything we can.
Excuse me.
Thanks.
Dear, take a seat.
Cuz.
Where have you been?
I've been looking for you.
Hey, aren't you going
to pay attention to me?
Aemie,
you should stay at my mansion for
now while your mom is recovering.
Is that okay?
Wait.
What about Zeke if cuz
stays at your mansion?
Not that I mean to meddle,
but shouldn't you ask her
husband for permission first?
Cuz, it's okay.
It's okay?
Oh.
Apparently, it's okay.
Then it's settled.
Aemie and you,
will live in the Ferrer Mansion.
Me? Even I am coming along?
Huh?
Welcome home.
It's beautiful, right?
Do you like your room?
It's okay.
I will let you settle down.
Cuz, aren't you planning
to finish your food?
What time do you want
to go to the hospital?
Aemie dear, do you want to shop?
Buy some clothes.
Let's have a relaxation day.
No.
I'm going to the hospital.
Come on, dear.
Don't stress yourself
out too much.
Besides, we need to bond
like mother and daughter.
No!
My mommy is still alive.
I don't need a substitute.
Oh, Cuz!
You haven't finished your food!
I pity her.
She's so down.
How about you, Amesyl?
Do you want to join
me for shopping?
I'll accompany
Cuz to the hospital.
Here.
Take it slow.
You really don't
remember anything?
Fauzia?
What happened anyway?
It might be better if I don't tell
you yet, that's what Doc said.
Apparently, the trauma makes you
unable to remember some of what
happened over the past few days.
Any news?
She's okay.
What about Boss?
How is he?
I don't know.
Lerwick and I still
haven't seen Boss.
So, it's still unclear what
our next plan of action is.
Excuse me, sir.
The patient needs to
take her medication now.
Okay.
Here's the water.
Slowly.
Are you okay?
Thank you.
Boss, we'll just be outside.
Do you know how much
I love your mom?
For twenty years.
I felt like I was going crazy.
Breathing...
but life felt meaningless.
Twenty hardest years.
Twenty long years
that I thought...
your mom was really gone.
I was happy when...
I found you.
And it's all thanks to Violet.
That night,
when Roswell introduced you to me.
Violet had already told me that
she had been looking for
your mom for a long time.
That night, I thought she had died.
We had no choice but to run.
Your mom and I got separated...
we sent her ahead
with your Auntie Sylvia.
We agreed...
to meet at the end of a bridge.
But, but...
but after the battle...
I couldn't find her.
I waited for so long.
But all that came was Violet.
Then she told me that
the Roswells had killed
your mom,
Sylvia,
Amesyl.
Roswells?
I'm sorry, dear.
But that's the truth.
The Roswells are our enemies.
But now that I have
you and your mom again,
I won't let you slip away again.
I don't understand, why
did you come here anyway?
I already told you, Jerson.
I'm just here to
check on Ezekiel.
Be careful.
There are a lot of Yaji
and Roswells here now.
Uhh. Excuse me.
You're Arcadia's nurse, right?
Yes, I am.
You know what to do.
I'll take care of it.
Alright, Jerson.
I'll go ahead.
- Wait.
- Oh?
It's too dangerous
for you to go alone.
I don't get why.
I mean, even if the
Roswells see me,
they don't know
I'm part of Swansea.
So, I'll be good.
Just relax, okay?
Okay. Hurry, okay?
Jerson.
Aux.
Why don't we just kill Arcadia?
Since we're already here anyway.
Let's just follow
Violet's plan for now.
Okay?
What are you looking at?
Let's go.
Ha...
Nothing.
I'm gonna have a smoke.
Ah, shit.
Miss Aemie.
Who are you visiting here?
Uhh.
I-I... You! You.
I was hoping it was you.
Ahh.
Uhh.
Are you following me?
It's just that, Miss Aemie...
Uh...
No, I'm not. It's just...
You're Ezekiel's friend, right?
Yes.
We used to be.
But we don't talk anymore.
You should be thankful.
Wait, hold on.
Just a moment, Miss Aemie.
Maybe you'd like to
have dinner with me first.
I still have something to do.
Oh.
Okay.
Aemie.
How do you feel?
I'm okay.
How about you?
Are you okay, Aemie?
You don't remember anything?
Yes.
But not totally.
When I got shot that—
Lee said is
what I don't remember.
Is there a problem, Fauzia?
Nothing.
Because—
because Ezekiel
might be looking for you.
Don't worry.
We're over.
I'm still waiting for someone.
What are you doing?
Aemie?
Eat.
You're looking pale.
Ma'am, excuse me.
The patient needs
to take her medicine—
I'll give her the medicine.
Oh, ma'am. I'm sorry.
- You can't—
- I am a BS Biology student.
I know about different drugs,
and how to administer
them properly.
So definitely...
I can manage giving
Miss Arcadia her dose.
I'll just have to give
her the medicine, right?
That's not so hard.
Give it to me.
Here, ma'am.
There's two medicines
she has to take.
I know.
Get out now.
I can handle it.
Do you have a...
history of hypertension?
Hypertension?
I don't think so.
Why?
Take this pain reliever...
so that you can
manage your injuries.
Aemie.
Hold on.
Didn't the nurse gave
you two medicines?
Don't worry.
She made a mistake.
You don't need it.
Just take a rest.
Love.
Do you know what
this meeting is for?
I have no idea.
I am the one who
called this meeting.
Shall we start?
First of all,
I invited everyone
for a celebration.
My dad has told me,
how much the Swanseas
have helped our family.
So, Auntie Violet...
from the bottom of my heart,
thank you.
You're always very welcome dear.
Anything for your daddy.
And to extend my
gratitude to the Swanseas,
From now on,
we will form an alliance.
Yaji and Swanseas
will work as one.
As the Yaji heiress,
I have the power to decide
our next steps moving forward.
Once my annulment with
Ezekiel Roswell is approved,
we'll start bringing
down the Roswells.
We will show no mercy.
We will take down
their businesses
and we'll take them down one by one.
This.
Is.
War.
We should wait for the queen to
wake up before we make any rash move.
We don't know what
the consequences could be—
Are you going against me,
Cassandra Heather?
No.
How disrespectful.
Excuse me?
What did you say?
You heard what I said.
You know what?
That's not disrespectful.
She was just making a—
Ladies, calm down.
Let's hear Aemie first.
Yeah, I'm listening but—
Enough!
We are launching a
war against the Roswells.
We'll bring down
Ezekiel Roswell once and for all!
It's so beautiful!
It's so pink! So beautiful!
It's so pink!
Just in case...
she won't wake up anymore.
Get out of my room.
We keep ending up together.
Oh, you.
Annulment?
Don't worry, dear.
I'll make the annulment
process quick.
[screams]
Mommy!
Don't shout, Baby Ae!
Oh!
Hey! Open this door!
Open this!
Who's this bitch?